http://www.nunnbush.com/shop/privacyPolicy.html#ca-privacy

Terms and Conditions
Digital Millennium Copyright Act (DMCA)
Terms and Conditions
Digital Millennium Copyright Act (DMCA)
NUNN BUSH PRIVACY POLICY
THIS PRIVACY POLICY DESCRIBES:
The categories of information Nunn Bush collects when you provide us information or use the Site.
The sources from which we collect personal information.
The purposes for which we collect personal information.
The categories of persons with whom we may share personal information.
How we place digital advertising.
I.	CATEGORIES OF PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT.
When you use the Site and when you place an order, we collect or receive personal information.
We describe those categories of personal information in more detail below.
1.1	Contact and Other Information Which Can Be Used to Identify You..
Nunn Bush collects information that you provide to us or one of our service providers when you use the Site.
We may collect your name, email address, IP address, mailing address, billing address, shipping address, telephone number, birthday month, account user ID or account password.
We may also collect the name and address of the recipient of a gift card you purchase. If you choose to create a Nunn Bush account or order products from the Site, you must provide your name and email address.
You may choose to submit your birthday month when you create a Nunn Bush account.
1.2	Commercial Information.
We collect information when you communicate with us about products, when you consider or place an order for our products or gift cards, when you place an item in your shopping cart, when you engage in Live Chats with us, when you call our call center and when you make on-line or in store purchases. We also maintain a record of your purchases.
1.3	Financial Information.
When you order Nunn Bush products from the Site, you will need to provide certain Financial Information to one of our third-party payment processers, Authorize.net, PayPal, Afterpay or Amazon Pay.
"Financial Information" includes your credit or debit card numbers, your PayPal or Amazon Pay account information, expiration dates and security codes.
Nunn Bush does not directly access, handle, or store your Financial Information.
However, Nunn Bush will receive certain personal information, which you provide to our Payment Processor, Authorize.net, PayPal, Afterpay, or Amazon Pay as necessary to finalize your order such as your name, address, mailing address, billing address, phone number and email address.
We will maintain a record of the purchases that you make when ordering from our Site.
1.4 Information Related to Your Use of our Site.
Nunn Bush may collect information regarding your interactions with and use of the Site. That information includes your electronic device identifier, hardware information, operating system version, browser type and version, browser language, media access control (MAC), screen resolution, cookie information, system type, search history on our website, access times, and referring website URLs. We also collect information when you use the store locator on our Site.
2.	THE SOURCES FROM WHICH WE COLLECT PERSONAL INFORMATION
We may collect personal information from the following sources:
2.1 Communications with You.
We collect personal information from you when you communicate with us by e-mail, regular mail or phone.
2.2	Use of Our Site.
We collect personal information you provide when you use the Site. For instance, at the end of the Site, we invite you to provide us with information so that we may contact you regarding your visit to the Site.
We collect personal information when you sign up for previews, offers, promotions and other electronic communications regarding our products.
We also collect personal information when you provide ratings and feedback regarding products and the Site.
2.3	Electronic Communications.
If you sign up to receive electronic communications, you consent to our sending such electronic communications to you using the email address you provide.
If you no longer want to receive electronic communications, you should use the “unsubscribe” button found on the emails you received or contact Nunn Bush Customer Service, and request to be unsubscribed.
Within ten (10) days of receipt of your unsubscribe request, Nunn Bush will remove you from our distribution list unless you request to be added again in the future.
You may also elect to receive text messages from us. When you sign up to receive text messages, we will send you information about promotional offers and more. To the extent, you voluntarily opt to have SMS notifications sent directly to your mobile phone, we receive and store the information you provide, including your telephone number or when you read a text message. You may opt out of receiving text messages at any time by texting “STOP” to our text messages. For more information about text messages, see our Terms and Conditions.
2.4	Your Nunn Bush Account.
We collect personal information when you create and use your Nunn Bush account.
2.5	When You Make a Purchase.
When you place an order on the Site, our service providers who provide payment processing services, PayPal, Amazon Pay or Afterpay, as applicable, will receive your Financial Information Nunn Bush does not receive your Financial Information when you make a purchase.
We do collect personal information required to finalize your order, such as your name, shipping address, telephone number, email address, and billing address.
We do not retain credit or debit card information you provide when you make a purchase in our stores or over the phone.
2.6	Gift Cards.
When you purchase a gift card through the Site, we collect any messages and other information that you may provide, such as the name and address of the gift card recipient.
Gift card purchases are subject to the terms of our gift card program.
2.7	On-Line Sweepstakes, Contests or Other Promotions.
When you choose to participate in our online sweepstakes, contests, or other promotions, you will need to submit certain personal information to enter, to receive any prize awarded and as otherwise specified in any official rules or other entry guidelines.
We may combine the personal information we receive when you enter our sweepstakes, contests, or other promotions with the information in your Nunn Bush account. We may also ask whether you wish to receive information about Nunn Bush promotions and products and you may opt-in to receive this information by checking the appropriate opt-in box.
If you choose to opt-in to receive communications, we will collect personal information and will use that personal information to send you information via email or regular mail about Nunn Bush promotions and products.
2.8	Live Chat.
We collect certain personal information when you use the Live Chat feature on the Site.
We collect such information from the transcript of that communication and other information that you may submit or input using that feature.
If you use a chat feature while signed into your Nunn Bush account, we may link the submitted information to your account.
2.9	Store Locator.
Nunn Bush uses the Google Maps API(s) as part of its "store locator" feature.
Pursuant to the Google Maps APIs Terms of Service, use of this location feature is also subject to Google's Privacy Policy.
For information on how Google categorizes location information, please visit "Types of location data used by Google."
Both the Google Maps APIs Terms of Service and Google’s Privacy Policy are incorporated into this Privacy Policy by reference.
2.10	Social Media Platforms.
We collect and store personal information when you post on our social media accounts, and we use personal information to serve marketing messages via those social media channels.
2.11	Use of Cookies.
We collect certain information using a variety of tools including, but not limited to, cookies, pixel tags/web beacons, search boxes, web forms and fields, clear GIFs and other technologies/methods.
If you turn off certain tools, you may not have access to features that make your experience on our Site more efficient and some of our features may not function properly.
(a)	Cookies. The Site may automatically use cookies to track your use of the Site.
We use cookies to facilitate and enhance your user experience on the Site and for other purposes described below.
"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored on your computer, tablet or cell phone device’s hard drive by your browser.
The Site may use both Cookies that we implement and Cookies implemented by our suppliers and other third parties.
We use Cookies to track how you access and use the Site, to learn when and how users visit the Site, to learn how frequently visitors view certain Site pages, to learn which search terms are used to find the Site, and to learn which websites direct you to the Site.
We also use Cookies to help display certain information on the Site and to improve your enjoyment of the Site, for example, by remembering your contact and other information when you access or use the Site.
Most browsers automatically accept Cookies.
You can disable this function, but disabling Cookies may impact your use and enjoyment of the Site.
(b)	Use of Cookies by Others. Our service providers may use Cookies and other tracking technologies, such as pixel tags, to track Site visitors across the Internet to understand how you get to the Site.
We do not have access or control over these Cookies and this Privacy Policy does not cover the use of Cookies placed by others.
(c)	"DO NOT TRACK" Signals. Some browsers have a “do not track” feature that allows you to tell a website that you do not want to have your online activities tracked.
Our Site does not support "do not track" requests.
3.	PURPOSES FOR WHICH WE COLLECT PERSONAL INFORMATION
We collect personal information for the following purposes:
3.1	Communications with You.
We use your personal information to respond to your requests or questions.
If you send Nunn Bush a question via email, or phone, create an account, engage in chat, send a letter or otherwise communicate with Nunn Bush, we will use that information to communicate with you.
We also use this personal information to provide marketing communications to you.
3.2	For Sales Transactions and to Process Your Orders.
We collect personal information to process and deliver your orders, and facilitate the return of purchased products in accordance with our company policies.
3.3	To Improve Our Products and Your Customer Experience.
We use the personal information we collect from you to improve our products and your customer experience.
3.4	Advertising, Marketing and Promotional Activities.
We use the information you provide to advertise, to develop marketing materials, to communicate with you about our products and to administer contests, promotions, events and surveys.
We also use this information to manage sweepstakes, contests, and other promotional activities if you choose to participate.
3.5	To Improve the Site and Your User Experience.
We use the personal information we collect to operate the Site and to improve your experience when you place an order from the Site or use the Site to obtain information.
We may use your personal information to develop and improve the content, materials, products, and services that we make available through the Site and the Site’s functionality, to inform you of marketing and communication plans and strategies, to evaluate user needs and customize Site content, and your browsing experience; and for other legitimate and lawful business purposes.
We use the personal information to help with proper Site function.
We may use Google Analytics to collect and process information about your use of the Site. Google sets cookies and then your web browser will automatically send data to Google. Google uses this data to provide us with reports that we use to improve the Site’s structure and content.
We may implement additional add-on services to Google Analytics, such as Demographics and Interest Reporting. Demographics and Interest Reporting uses Cookies to collect data about our Site traffic by tracking users across websites and across time to provide us with analytics on our user base.
To learn more about how Google uses data, visit Google’s Privacy Policy. You may download the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on for each web browser you use, but this does not prevent the use of other analytics tools.
We may use other third-party analytic tools to process information about your use of the Site, including when you visit the Site, URLs of the websites that you visit prior to visiting the Site and when you visit those websites, and IP addresses assigned to the devices from where you access the Internet.
Our analytics providers may set and read Cookies to collect this data and your web browser will automatically send data collected by those Cookies to our analytics providers.
This information is used for our own internal purposes to improve the content of this Site, to enhance users’ experience when visiting our Site, and to customize the content and/or layout of our pages.
All information of user behavior described in this section will be recorded on a group basis, and is not personally identifiable.
We may combine information collected by third-party analytics with other information, including personal information.
We will treat such combined information as personal information.
3.6	To Provide Targeted Advertising.
We use third parties to provide internet-based advertising services. These services collect data about your interactions with the Site and other websites to send you targeted advertisements for goods and services. The data collected may be associated with your personal information. These advertisements may appear on the Site and on other websites and may be sent to you via email.
For example, we may use Google Ads to serve ads across various websites. Google uses Cookies to collect data about your visits to the Site to generate targeted advertisements to you on other websites that you visit. To opt-out of this type of advertising by Google, to customize your ad preferences, or to limit Google’s collection or use of such data, visit Google’s Safety Center and Google’s Ad Settings and follow Google’s personalized ad opt-out instructions. Opting out will not affect your use of the Site.
To change your preferences with respect to certain online ads and to obtain more information about third-party ad networks and online behavioral advertising, visit National Advertising Initiative Consumer opt-out page or the Digital Advertising Alliance Self-Regulatory Program. Changing your settings with individual browsers or ad networks will not necessarily carry over to other browsers or ad networks. As a result, depending on the opt-outs you request, you may still see our ads.
3.7	Rakuten Advertising.
We may use Rakuten Advertising to collect information when you interact with our digital property, including IP addresses, digital identifiers, information about your web browsing, and app usage and how you interact with our properties and ads for a variety of purposes such as personalization of offers or advertisements, analytics about how you engage with websites or ads, and other commercial purposes.
For more information about Rakuten Advertising’s collection, use, and sale of your personal information and your rights please see the following links: https://rakutenmarketing.com/legal-notices/services-privacy-policy/ and https://rakutenmarketing.com/legal-notices/subject-requests/.
3.8	Information Regarding Your Orders.
We use personal information to allow you to place orders, to communicate with you about your purchase, account information, shipping information or for customer service reasons.
3.9	To Protect our Legal Rights and the Rights of Others.
We may use personal information to protect our legal rights or interests, or those of others, including to bring a legal action against you or anyone who may be causing harm to us, the Site, or other users of the Site.
3.10	Accommodations.
To accommodate your requests for ADA related accommodations when you use the Site.
4.	WHEN WE SHARE PERSONAL INFORMATION
We limit with whom we share your personal information.
We will not sell your personal information.
We may share your Information, including your personal information, with the following persons or entities:
4.1	Employees and Affiliates.
We may share personal information with our employees, independent contractors and affiliated companies for purposes of responding to your requests, to assist with your orders and to assist with the operation of our Site, our stores and our business.
4.2	Service Providers.
We may share your personal information, with providers which perform services for us.
We use service providers for order fulfillment, payment processing, fraud prevention, advertising, professional services, print media providers, product reviews, live chat, packaging and mailing products or marketing materials, website hosting, SMS marketing communications service providers, and other service providers needed to operate our business and meet your customer service needs.
4.3	Social Media and Digital Advertising Companies.
We also may share your information with advertising technology providers, social media companies, user experience providers, digital retargeting providers, and data enrichment providers.
4.4	Legal Requirements.
We may use your Information and share it with third parties to the extent required by applicable law, including in the event of a subpoena, court order, or law enforcement request.
We will use the Information and share it with third parties if we believe doing so is necessary to operate the Site or to protect our rights or the rights of others, including disclosing information necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action in the event of a violation of our contracts, terms, or policies.
4.5	Business Transactions.
All Information we collect from you when you use the Site is exclusively the property of Nunn Bush.
If Nunn Bush undergoes a change in control, acquisition, merger, reorganization, bankruptcy or asset sale, all Information owned by or in the control of Nunn Bush may be transferred, sold, shared, or otherwise disclosed to the successor of the transaction.
5.	USING AND DISCLOSING DE-IDENTIFIED OR AGGREGATED INFORMATION.
Nunn Bush may collect, use, share, transfer and otherwise process de-identified and aggregated information that it receives or creates for any purposes in its sole discretion, in compliance with applicable laws.
Nunn Bush is the sole and exclusive owner of such de-identified and aggregated information, including if we de-identify the information so that it is no longer considered personal information under applicable laws.
We may combine Information you give us with other Information from Nunn Bush sources, transactions and communications.
This may include, but is not limited to, information from Nunn Bush stores, direct mail, catalogs, emails, SMS/MMS messages, special events, products and applications, or other Nunn Bush interactions.
We may aggregate personal information and other Information.
We will not re-identify that personal information and other Information once aggregated.
6.	SECURITY.
Nunn Bush uses commercially reasonable efforts to protect your personal information.
Nunn Bush and its third-party service providers have implemented security measures to help protect against the risk of loss, misuse or alteration of any Information under Nunn Bush's control.
Nunn Bush uses industry standard encryption protocols to safeguard the security of your transactions.
YOU UNDERSTAND THAT NO DATA TRANSMISSION OVER THE INTERNET OR DEVICE CAN BE GUARANTEED TO BE 100% SECURE.
WHILE WE STRIVE TO PROTECT PERSONAL INFORMATION, WE DO NOT GUARANTEE THE SECURITY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION AND YOU PROVIDE PERSONAL INFORMATION AT YOUR OWN RISK.
7.	ONLINE ADVERTISING.
Nunn Bush participates in interest-based advertising, tailored to how you browse or shop, or you may see advertising for Nunn Bush on other websites based on your browser behavior across websites.
Some websites where Nunn Bush may advertise belong to ad networks that use your web browsing history to choose which ads to display on their network websites.
Those ads include advertising for Nunn Bush.
Some personal information may be used to help us advertise to you.
Other sites where you see our ads, such as Facebook, may use interest preferences that you have chosen on those sites, as well as registration and other information about you, to choose which ads to display to you.
Information collected by our advertising service providers through Cookies and other technologies may include browsing behavior, referring sites and your response to advertisements. The information we collect in this manner is used to improve our advertising.
If you receive a targeted advertisement, you may click on the displayed icon to receive more information and you may choose to opt-out.
Your opt-out choices may be affected by your use of a specific device, your browser settings or your log-on credentials.
Please refer to the website that you are visiting, your browser and/or your device settings for additional information.
If you opt out, you may still receive online advertising from Nunn Bush, which is based on your preferences or online behavior.
Nunn Bush uses multiple online advertising programs, so opting out of one program does not opt you out from all online advertising.
8.	THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES.
For your convenience, the Site may link to, or be linked to, websites not maintained or controlled by Nunn Bush.
This does not imply any affiliation with, or an endorsement, authorization, sponsorship or promotion of a non-Nunn Bush website or its owner.
Nunn Bush is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third parties or any third-party websites.
If you choose to access third-party websites, you do so at your own risk, and you should read the terms and conditions and privacy policies for each website that you visit.
9. SOCIAL MEDIA WEBSITES.
Nunn Bush participates in social media platforms such as Facebook®, Twitter®, Instagram® and YouTube® that enable online sharing and collaboration among customers. This Site may allow you to connect to and share information with these various social media platforms. These features may require us to implement Cookies, plug-ins, and application protocol interfaces (APIs) provided by those social media platforms to facilitate those communications and features.
By choosing to use any third-party social media platform or choosing to share content or communications with any social media platform, you allow us to share information with the designated social media platform. We cannot control any policies or terms of any third-party platforms. As a result, we cannot be responsible for any use of your Information or content by a third-party platform, which you use at your own risk.
10.	ACCESS BY CHILDREN.
The Site is not directed at children.
Nunn Bush does not knowingly collect, use, or share personal information from children under thirteen (13) years old.
If a parent or legal guardian learns that their child provided us with personal information without his or her consent, please contact us.
11.	ACCESS FROM OUTSIDE THE UNITED STATES.
The Site is intended for consumers within the United States. If you access the Site from outside the United States, pleased be aware that personal information may be transferred to, stored in, and processed in the United States.
12.	HOW TO CONTACT NUNN BUSH.
You may contact Nunn Bush with questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy and this Site as set forth below:
Nunn BushPrivacy Policy and Data Protection Officer333 W Estabrook BlvdGlendale, WI 53212www.nunnbush.comEmail:
NunnBushPrivacyPolicy@weycogroup.com877-557-0062
Nunn Bush RESERVES THE RIGHT TO MODIFY THIS PRIVACY POLICY AT ANY TIME.
ALL CHANGES WILL BE EFFECTIVE IMMEDIATELY UPON POSTING THE CHANGED OR AMENDED PRIVACY POLICY TO THE SITE.
BY ACCESSING OR USING THE SITE FOLLOWING THE POSTING YOU UNDERSTAND SUCH CHANGES APPLY TO YOU.
13. TERMS APPLICABLE TO CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS ONLY.
This Section provides additional terms that apply to residents of California. In the event of a conflict between this Section and the remainder of this Policy, this Section shall take precedence for California residents. In this Section only, any capitalized terms not defined in this Policy have the meanings set forth in the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (the “CCPA”).
13.1 We Do Not “Sell” Your Personal Information.
In the last 12 months we have not Sold your Personal Information and we currently do not Sell Personal information. You have the right to opt-out of the Sale of your Personal Information by businesses subject to the CCPA.
13.2 Categories of Personal Information Collected.
In the last 12 months, we collected the following categories of Personal information. See the section above titled “Categories of Personal information We Collect” for more detail on the type of Personal information in each category.
Contact and Other Information Which Can Be Used to Identify You
Commercial Information
Financial Information
Information Related to Your Use of the Site
13.3 Categories of Personal Information Disclosed for a Business Purpose.
In the last 12 months, we disclosed the following categories of Personal Information for our Business Purposes. See the section above titled “Categories of Personal Information We Collect” for more detail on the type of Personal Information in each category.
Contact and Other Information Which Can Be Used to Identify You
Commercial Information
Financial Information
Information Related to Your Use of the Site
13.4 Your Rights to Request and Know and Your Right to Request Deletion.
Under the CCPA, California residents have additional rights with regard to their personal information. We have provided a summary of those rights below:
(a)	Right to Request and Know. You have a right to request that we disclose any of the following types of information for interactions which occurred in the prior 12-month period prior to the date of your request: (a) the categories of personal information we collected from you, (b) the categories of sources from which the personal information was collected, (c) the business or commercial purpose for collecting your personal information, (d) the categories of third parties with whom we shared your personal information (e) the specific pieces of personal information we collected from you (i.e., “data portability”), and (f) a list of categories of personal information we disclosed for a Business Purpose in the last 12 months.
(b)	Right to Request Deletion. You have a right to request that we delete personal information we collected from you by submitting a verifiable request following the instructions in 15.2 below. We will comply with such request, and direct our service providers to do the same, subject to certain exceptions permitted by applicable law.
(c)
Right to Opt-Out of the Sale of Personal information. Under California law, consumers have the right to opt-out of the Sale of their personal information. However, we do not sell your personal information.
(d)	Right to Non-Discrimination. You have the right to non-discrimination for the exercise of your consumer Privacy Rights under the CCPA.
13.5 How to Exercise Your Rights to Know and Your Right to Request Deletion.
(a)	How to Exercise Your Rights to Know and your Rights to Request Deletion:
To exercise your rights to know and your rights to request deletion described in this Privacy Policy, you may submit your request to us by contacting us at any of the following:
Toll Free Call.
You can call us toll-free at 877-557-0062.
Once you call, there will be a menu # assigned to CCPA requests so our customer service team can respond and start processing your CCPA request.
Email.
You can also email us at NunnBushPrivacyPolicy@weycogroup.com. Once we receive your email, we will acknowledge your request and start processing your CCPA request.
(b)	Verifiable Consumer Request. In order to verify your request to know or your request to delete, you must provide sufficient information that allows us to reasonably verify you are the person about whom we collected personal information and you must describe your request with sufficient detail to allow us to properly understand, evaluate, and respond to it You must provide your first and last name, your home address, and the linked email account(s) to NunnBush.com.
Please note however, that we may request additional information as necessary to confirm your identity.
(c)	Who May Exercise Your Rights? You may only make a request to exercise your rights on behalf of yourself.
A parent or legal guardian may make a request on behalf of their child.
If you are a California resident, only you or a person registered with the California Secretary of State that you authorize to act on your behalf may make a request related to your personal information.
See the section titled "Authorized Agents" below for more information.
(d)	When We Will Respond. We will acknowledge your request within 10 business days of receipt.
We will try to respond to your request within 45 calendar days of the date of receipt of the request. If we cannot verify your request within that 45-calendar day time period, we may deny your request.
If we require additional time, we will inform you of the reason and extension period prior to the original 45 calendar day response period.
Any disclosures we provide will only cover the 12-month period preceding our receipt of your request.
For data portability requests, we will select a format to provide your personal information to you.
We may charge a fee to process or respond to your request if it is excessive, repetitive, or manifestly unfounded.
13.6	Authorized Agents.
You may designate an authorized agent to make a request on your behalf to exercise your rights under the CCPA by doing the following: (1) provide the authorized agent written permission to do so; and (2) verify your own identity (per the process stated above), as well as the identity of the authorized agent directly.
Alternatively, your authorized agent may provide us with a copy of a power of attorney issued pursuant to California Probate Code sections 4000 to 4465. We may deny a request from an authorized agent if we do not have proof that they are authorized by you to act on your behalf.
13.7	Shine The Light.
If you are a California resident, you are permitted, pursuant to California Civil Code Section 1798.83, to obtain:
(a) a list of all third parties that Nunn Bush may have disclosed your personal information to, within the past year, for direct marketing purposes; and (b) a description of the categories of personal information disclosed.
To obtain such information, please email your request to the contact information set forth above in the "How to Contact Nunn Bush" section. Any such request must include “California Privacy Rights Request” in the first line of the description and include your name, street address, city, state, and ZIP code.
Please note that we are only required to respond to one request per customer each year, and we are not required to respond to requests made by means other than through this email address or mail address.
14.	Contact for More Information
If you have questions or concerns about our California privacy policies and practices, please contact us as follows:
Nunn BushPrivacy Policy and Data Protection Officer333 W Estabrook BlvdGlendale, WI 53212www.nunnbush.comEmail:
NunnBushPrivacyPolicy@weycogroup.com877-557-0062
Privacy Policy Last Updated: July 1, 2020.
